http://www.lawrence.edu/s/privacy

Additional Privacy Rights Notice
Lawrence University Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy explains how Lawrence University collects and uses information gathered when you use Lawrence University websites, apps or other online services.
Information Collected
We automatically collect and store certain non-personal information while you use the Lawrence website and services. We use this information primarily to monitor the use of these systems and to make improvements. Individual names are not collected. Host names and/or IP addresses are collected and only associated with individual users where required to do so by law, to protect and defend our rights or property, or in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any individual. This information may include your browser type, domain names, IP address, unique device identifier, search criteria used, content viewed, and the emails and phone numbers that you contact through the Website, the pages you view, access times and referring website addresses.
Information collection methods may use various technologies such as cookies, server logs, url parameters, tracking images, web forms for information submission and web analytics services.  Your browser may allow you to disable some of these collection methods.
When requesting information, assistance or registering for events you may be asked to submit your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to allow Lawrence University to respond to your request. Lawrence University does not market to children under 13 years and we request that children under age 13 not submit personal data to us through our websites.
Information Use
We may use the information we collect from you when you voluntarily submit data to Lawrence University, respond to a survey or marketing communication or use Lawrence University web services:
To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content in which you are most interested.
To improve our website by monitoring activity, usage trends, detect abuse and for other system administration tasks.
To process and respond to your requests, questions and to send information to you.
Lawrence University will not share, sell, rent or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes.
Lawrence University uses third party services to provide and improve web and communication services for our users.  These services, like Google Analytics, are used to monitor site usage, web traffic, visitor behavior and trends to optimize web services for visitors.  For more information about Google Analytics please see Google’s privacy policy, Google Analytics Cookie Usage on Websites and Google’s terms of use.
Information may also be provided to third parties when doing so is necessary to satisfy applicable laws, regulations, legal process or government request.  In addition, information may be shared when required to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues or when required to protect the rights and the safety of the university, visitors, students and employees.
Third Party Websites
The Lawrence University website may include links to third party websites and services. These third party sites and services have separate and independent privacy policies and terms of use, which we encourage you to review.
Additional Rights You May Have
You may have additional data protection rights concerning your data.  For example, the European Union has created the General Data Protection Regulation that provides certain rights regarding data use and collection.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
This privacy policy may be updated periodically.  All privacy policy changes will be updated on the Privacy Policy page.
Contacting Us and Communications from Lawrence University
If you are receiving information from Lawrence University and wish to unsubscribe from receiving future messages, you can contact the Communications Office at communications@lawrence.edu. You may also follow the instructions included at the bottom of each email sent by Lawrence and we will promptly remove you from correspondence channels.
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
